<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string-array name="places">
        <item>Angkot ABG</item>
        <item>Angkot ADL</item>
        <item>Angkot AG</item>
        <item>Angkot AL</item>
        <item>Angkot AMG</item>
        <item>Angkot CKL</item>
        <item>Angkot GA</item>
        <item>Angkot GL</item>
        <item>Angkot GML</item>
        <item>Angkot LDG</item>
        <item>Angkot LG</item>
        <item>Angkot MK</item>
        <item>Angkot MM</item>
        <item>Angkot GM</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_desc">
        <item>Arjosari - Borobudur - Gadang</item>
        <item>Arjosari - Dinoyo - Landungsari</item>
        <item>Arjosari - Gadang</item>
        <item>Arjosari - Landungsari</item>
        <item>Arjosari - Mergosono - Gadang</item>
        <item>Cemorokandang - Landungsari</item>
        <item>Gadang - Arjosari</item>
        <item>Gadang - Landungsari</item>
        <item>Gadang - Mergan - Landungsari</item>
        <item>Landungsari - Dinoyo - Gadang</item>
        <item>Landungsari - Gadang</item>
        <item>Mulyorejo - Karang Besuki</item>
        <item>Madyopuro - Mulyorejo</item>
        <item>Gadang - Madyopuro</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="place_details">
        <item>Term Arjosari – Jl. Simp. RP Suroso – Jl. R. Intan – Jl. A. Yani – Jl. Borobudur – Jl. Sukarno Hatta – Jl. Cengkeh – Jl. Kalpataru – Jl. Melati – Jl. Mawar – Jl. Saranagan – Jl. Tawangmangu – Jl. Kaliurang – Jl. WR. Supratman – Jl. P. Sudirman – Jl. Pattimuara – JL. Trunojoyo – Jl. Jembatan Pahlawan – Jl. Gatot Subroto – Jl. L. Martadinata – Jl. Kol Sugiyono – Term Gadang
        </item>
        <item>
            Terminal Arjosari - Jl. Simpang R. Panji Suroso - Jl. Raden Intan - Jl. Jend. A. Yani - Jl. Letjen S. Parman – Jl. Letjen Sutoyo – Jl. W. R. Supratman – Jl. Panglima Sudirman – Jl. Patimura – Jl. Trunojoyo- Jl. Kertanegara – Jl. Kahuripan –  Jl Semeru – Jl. Ijen – Jl. Bandung – Jl. Terusan Bogor – Jl. Mayjen Panjahitan – Jl. Mayjen Haryono – Jl. Tlogomas – Terminal Landung Sari
        </item>
        <item>

Terminal Arjosari – Jl. Simpang R. Panji Suroso – Jl. Raden Intan – Jl. Jend A. Yani – Jl. Letjen S. Parma – Jl. Letjen Sutuyo – Jl. Jagung Suprapto – Jl. Basuki Rahmat – Merdeka Utara – Jl. Merdeka Timur – Jl. Sukarjowiryor   Panoto – Jl. Pasar Besar – Jl. Sersan Harun – Jl. Prof Moh yamin – Jl. Sartono SH – Jl. Kol Sugiono – Terminal Gadang

        </item>
        <item>

Terminal Arjosari – Jl. R. Panji Suroso – Jl. Laksda Adi Sucipto – Jl. Tenaga – Jl. Karya Timur – Jl. Mahakam – Jl. W. R. Supratman – Jl. Panglima Sudirman – Jl. Patimura – Jl. Trunojoyo – Jl. Kertanegara – Jl. Tugu – Jl. Kahuripan – Jl. Semeru – Jl. Ijen – Jl. Retawu – Jl. Bondowoso – Jl. Jombang – Jl. Suroboyo – Jl. Jakarta – Jl. Bogor –  Jl. Veteran – Jl. Sumbersari – Terminal Landung Sari

        </item>
        <item>

Term Arjosari – Jl. Simp SP. Suroso – Jl. S. Priyo Sudarmo – Jl. RT Suryo – Jl. Hamid Rusdi – Jl. Kesatriaan Terusan – Jl. Urip Sumoharjo – Jl. P. Sudirman – Jl. Ir Juanda – Jl. Kebalon – Jl. Kol Sugiyono – Term Gadang

        </item>
        <item>

APK Cemoro Kandang – Jl. Raya Cemoro Kandang – Jl. Raya Madyopuro – Jl. Sekarpuro – Jl. Komplek UNIDA – JL. D. Sentani – Jl. D. Tigi – Jl. D. Kerinci – Jl. D. Tondano – Jl. Limboto – Jl. Raya Sawojajar – Jl. Ranu Grati – Jl. M. Wiyono – Jl. Kesatrian – Jl. Hamid Rusdi – Jl. RT. Suryo – Jl. S. Priyo Sudarmo – Jl. Ciliwung – Jl. L. Sutoyo – Jl. Kedawung – Jl. Kalpataru – Jl. Cengkeh – Jl. Sukarno Hatta – Jl. Simp Panggung – Jl. Vinolia – Jl. Keramik – Jl. MT. Haryono - Jl. Tlogomas – Term Landungsari

        </item>

        <item>
Terminal Gadang – Jl. Satsuit Tubun – Jl. S Supriyadi – Jl. Arif Margono – Jl. Ade Irma Suryani –Jl. KH Wahid Hasyim –Jl. Kauman – Jl. Hasyim Asyhari – Jl. AR Hakim  - Jl. Merdeka Utara – Jl. S Wiryop
ranoto – Jl. Mojopahit – Jl. Tugu – Jl. Untung Suropati – Jl. Pajajaran – Jl. Truno Joyo – Jl. Cokroaminoto – Jl. Dr Cipto – Jl. Pang Sudirman – Jl. WR Supratman – Jl. Letjend Sutoyo – Jl. Letjend S. Parman – Jl. Jend Ayani – Jl. R Intan – Terminal Arjosari
</item>
        <item>Term. Gadang –Jl. S Tubun –Jl. S. Supriadi –Jl. Janti –Sonokeling. –Jl. Niaga –Jl. Susanto –Jl. Halmahera –Jl. Sampo –Jl. Kalimantan –Jl. Sulawesi –Jl. Yulius Usman –Jl. Arief Margono –Jl. KH. Hasyim Asyari –Jl. Kawi –Jl. Ijen –Jl. Retawu –Jl. Gede –Jl. Jakarta –Jl. Garut –Jl. Bandung –Jl. Veteran –Jl. Sumbersari –Jl. Gajayana –Jl. MT> Hartono –Jl. Raya Tlogomas –Term Landungsari.</item>
        <item>Term Gadang – Jl. Satsuit Tubun – Jl. S. Supriyadi – Jl. Janti – Jl. Sono Keling – Jl. Niaga – Jl. Susanto – Jl. Halmahera – Jl. Tanimbar – Jl. Sulawesi – Jl. Nusakambangan – Jl. Arief Margono – Jl. S. Supriyadi – Jl. Rajawali – Term Mergan Lori – Jl. Raya Langsep – Jl. Galunggunbg – Jl. Bukit Barisan – Jl. Tamboro – Jl. Tidar – Jl. Simpang Candi  - Jl. Candi – Jl. Ters. Sigura-gura – Jl. Belakang IAIN – Jl. Mertoijoyo Selatan – Jl. Mertojoyo – Jl. MT Haryono Gg XII- Jl. Raya Tlogomas – Term Landungsari</item>
        <item>
Terminal Landung Sari – Jl. Mayjen MT. Haryono – Jl. Mayjen Panjahitan – Jl. Brigjen S. Riyadi – Jl. Jend Basuki Rahmat – Jl. Merdeka Barat – Jl. Kauman – Jl. Syarif al Qodri – Jl. Ade Irma Suryani – Jl. Pasar Besar – Jl. Sersan Harun – Jl. Prof. Moh. Yamin – Jl. Sartono SH – Jl. Kol. Sugiono – Terminal Gadang
</item>
        <item>
Terminal Landungsari – Jl. Tlogo Mas – Jl. Mayjend Haryono Jl. Sumber Sari – Jl. Bendungan Sutami – Jl. Surabaya - Jl. Bondowoso – Jl. Gading – Jl. Wilis – Jl. Panderman – Jl. AR Hakim – Jl. Merdeka Utara – Jl. Merdeka Selatan – Jl. Wiryopranoto – Jl. Sultan  Syahrir – Jl. Kyai Tamin – Jl. Sartono SH – Jl. Peltu Sujono – Jl. Susanto – Jl. Niaga – Jl. Sonokeling – Jl. Janti – Jl. S. Supriyadi – Jl. Satsuit Tubun – Terminal Gadang
</item>
        <item>
Term Madyopuro – Jl. Kiageng Gribik – Jl. Muharto – Jl. Z. Zakse – Jl. Pasar Besar – Jl. Zaenal Arifin – Jl. A Munandar – Jl. MGR Sugriwiryopranoto – Jl. Merdeka Timur – Jl. Merdeka Selatan – Jl. Kauman – Jl. KH Hasyim Asyhari – Jl. Kawi – Jl. Ijen – Jl. Pahlawan Trib – Jl. Surabaya – Jl. B. Sutami – Jl. Kleseman – APK Karang Besuki
</item>
        <item>
Term Mulyorejo – Jl. Raya Bandulan – Jl. Jupri – Jl. Raya Langsep – Jl. Raya Dieng – Jl. Kawi Atas – Jl. Kawi – Jl. A.R. Hakim – Jl. Merdeka Utara – Jl. MGR. Sugriwiryopranoto – Jl. Mojopahit – Jl. Tugu – Jl. Kertanegara – Jl. Trunojoyo – Jl. Pattimura – Jl. Urip Sumoharjo – Jl. M. Wiyono – Jl. Ranu Grati – Jl. Danau Toba – Jl. Ki Ageng Gribig – Term Madyopuro
</item>
        <item>

Term. Gadang – Jl. Kol. Sugiono . – Jl. Susanto – Jl. Irian Jaya – Jl. Tanimbar. – Jl. Sulaesi. – Jl. Yulius Usman . – Jl. Syarief Al Qodri – Jl. A. I Suryani – Jl. B. Katamso – Jl. Ir Rais – Jl. Jupri – Jl. Bandulan – Jl. Raya Mulyrejo – Sub term Mulyorejo.
</item>


    </string-array>

    <array name="places_picture">
        <item>@drawable/a</item>
        <item>@drawable/b</item>
        <item>@drawable/c</item>
        <item>@drawable/d</item>
        <item>@drawable/e</item>
        <item>@drawable/f</item>
        <item>@drawable/g</item>
        <item>@drawable/h</item>
        <item>@drawable/i</item>
        <item>@drawable/j</item>
        <item>@drawable/k</item>
        <item>@drawable/l</item>
        <item>@drawable/m</item>
        <item>@drawable/n</item>

    </array>
</resources>